You need to pay attention to this chart
right here. Because every 4 years, like
clockwork, this exact candle prints and
then explodes markets to the upside
beyond belief. It happens every single
cycle at exactly the same moment. It
takes the world by storm. It explodes
prices to the upside and everyone is
left wondering, "How did that happen?"
I'm going to show you the exact pattern.
Take a look. In 2015, we had the bottom
of the market right here with this
candle. The next candle was a bullish
engulfing candle, which absolutely
exploded the markets into the bull run.
Next happened 4 years later. This red
candle, bottom of the market. The next
candle, bullish engulfing candle, sent
shockwaves into the market, exploded
prices to the upside, and was a
full-fledged bull run. 4 years later,
exact same thing. This red candle,
bottom of the market. Next candle,
bullish engulfing candle. That was the
beginning of the bull run. That sent
shockwaves through the market. That
exploded prices. And I'm going to tell
you in this video when the next one is
scheduled to happen. But more
importantly, I have a huge warning about
the next bull run that I need to share
with you. So, let's get into it. By the
way, we are getting tons of comments
about when bottom and altcoins. Did you
know I give my top altcoin picks [music]
and my big secret investment, both
covered in the Bitcoin Bottom Blueprint.
Just my big secret investment alone is
already worth multiple times the cost of
the Bitcoin Bottom Blueprint. But on top
of that, you get my top altcoin picks.
And on top of that, you get one
guaranteed buy inside of the golden zone
or your money back. Public launch coming
soon. Watch your email.
So, here we are. Bitcoin US Dollar
Index. And today, we are on the 6th
month chart. Meaning, each candle
represents 6 months of price action.
What I have to share with you in this
video today is going to upset you. I
have some bad news about the next bull
run that you're not going to want to
hear. But, you're also going to really,
really want to hear when the next bull
run is going to happen. When is that
next bullish engulfing candle going to
print? Because in the exact formula, it
happens like clockwork at exactly the
same particular market situation. In
order to truly understand what we're
dealing with right here, we're going to
start our journey back in 2015. First
and foremost, let's address what is a
bullish engulfing candle. A few things
need to be true in order to have a real
bullish engulfing candle. First, the
candle has to be green. Second, the
candle before it has to be red. Third,
the body of the green candle needs to be
bigger than the body of the red candle.
Notice how I didn't say anything about
the wicks. The wicks are these lines
here, which tell you everything you need
to know about momentum, but they're not
important to this topic, which is a
bullish engulfing candle. In other
words, we had three check marks. This is
green? Yes. This is red? Yes. The green
body is bigger than the red body? Yes.
All three are yes, it's a bullish
engulfing candle. How about the next
one? Is the next one bullish engulfing
candle? No, the previous candle's not
red, right? So, all three have to be
true. Bullish engulfing candles are very
rare. In fact, when you're looking on
the chart here, they happen at exactly
the same time in the market cycle, like
clockwork. It happens right after the
bottoming candle. That one candle, that
red candle, that's the worst candle.
Right after that worst of the worst is
the best of the best. It's the start of
the bull run. It's the moment everybody
wants. We're going to hone in on two
things today. We're going to hone in on
when I think this candle is going to
print, and then we're going to hone in
on the bad, bad news that I have to
share with you about the next bull run.
And I'll leave you with the video of
what I think you should do with that
information. So, those are the three
things we're going to really knock out
of the park in this video. So, let's
really address this bullish engulfing
candle. You see, 4 years later, we had
printed this candle back in 2015. 4
years later, in 2019, we did it again.
We had the top of a market. We had a
couple bad red candles. This one, back
in July 2018, marked the bottom of the
market. And the next candle, it was
green? Yes. Previous candle red? Yes.
Was the green body bigger than the red
body? All three, yes. Bullish engulfing
candle, that started the bull run, plain
and simple. That candle started at about
3,000 and it went up to 71,000,
70,000, whatever, 69,000. All with this
bullish engulfing candle. And then the
whole thing repeated 4 years later. Take
a look. This candle, July 2022, bottom
of the market. No ifs, ands, or buts
about it. Back when we were at 15, 16,
17,000, everybody said I was crazy to
call the bottom. Recently, many of you
have been randomly unsubscribed from my
channel. And missing just one video in a
market like this can cost you big time.
So, stop what you're doing, look down,
and make sure you are subscribed. We
have to give credit to the system that I
use. The system that I use for bottoms
of the market is incredible. I've been
using this system for years and years
and years and years, and that's how you
create real wealth. That's why I'm
releasing my Bitcoin bottom blueprint.
The bottom of the market, so important.
We had that in July 2022. The next
candle, it was green? Yes. The previous
candle was red? Yes. The bottom of this
green candle was bigger? We've got
ourselves a bullish engulfing candle. In
other words, every single cycle, the
devastation ends the same way. The
devastation ends when we print a bullish
engulfing candle, which starts the bull
run. In other words, that's the best
time to invest. The The best time to
invest is at the start of the bull. This
is quite literally the secrets to
success right here. Not only am I going
to share with you when that's scheduled
to happen, but I'm also going to share
the really bad news about the next bull,
and what should you do with this
information? We're here. 2023 is the
last time that we had this candle. And
the next one is scheduled to happen 4
years later. In other words, drumroll,
please. The next bullish engulfing
candle is scheduled to happen towards
the end of 2026 and potentially in the
beginning of 2027. It's going to fall
right in that zone of time. So, look at
the end of this year, look at Q1 2027.
That's when the next bullish engulfing
candle is set to take form. But, it
doesn't end there, because that's going
to start the bull, and everybody's going
to get excited. That's the best time to
invest. You want to see prices explode.
You want to see prices go up. But, I'm
here to tell you, based on a lot of
evidence in the charts, and a lot of
facts that I have been studying, I've
got some very, very bad news about the
next bull run. Your favorite altcoins,
your favorite cryptos, the market that
you love, the market that you watch
every day, you've been watching for
years, you've been dreaming about
generational wealth, you've been
dreaming about a million-dollar Bitcoin,
you've been dreaming about half a
million-dollar Bitcoin, you've been
dreaming, and you can't wait until 2029,
2030 for Bitcoin to be up near million
dollars, to be a half a million, for you
to be swimming in profits, for you to be
able to buy that dream home because
Bitcoin has risen so much. I'm here to
tell you, it will not happen that way.
It will not happen that way. We will not
see a million-dollar Bitcoin by 2030. I
know that that's a huge [snorts]
thing in social media, and it seems like
an obvious thing, that it will
definitely have a million-dollar
Bitcoin. Everybody's talking about it.
Some of the most wealthy people on
planet Earth have predicted it. We're
not going to get even close. That's
right. I said it. We're not even going
to get close. And clip this, mark this,
put a folder here, come back and watch
this in 2027. You're going to look down,
you're going to see a bullish engulfing
candle. We're on the right track. We
will have a bull run. We will have
prices rise, but it will be unlike
anything we've seen before. It will be
weaker than all of the previous cycles
we've had before. Don't just take my
word for it. Look at the facts. You
can't escape the facts. Look at the
facts in the charts. We're not going to
see a million-dollar Bitcoin. In fact, I
really doubt we'll see a half a
million-dollar Bitcoin. More on my
predictions, let me know in the
comments, but you better mark this video
and you better come back to watch it in
2027 and beyond. By the way, we are
getting tons of comments about win
bottom and altcoins. Did you know I give
my top altcoin picks and my big secret
investment both covered in the Bitcoin
Bottom Blueprint. Just my big secret
investment alone is already worth
multiple times the cost of the Bitcoin
Bottom Blueprint. But on top of that,
you get my top altcoin picks. And on top
of that, you get one guaranteed buy
inside of the golden zone or your money
back. Public launch coming soon. Watch
your email.